<export xmlns="http://de.fhg.iais.roberta.blockly"><program><block_set xmlns="http://de.fhg.iais.roberta.blockly" robottype="calliope" xmlversion="3.1" description="" tags=""><instance x="175" y="123"><block type="robControls_start" id="*nuF1y^y7}=kT9riuhX]" intask="true" deletable="false"><mutation declare="true"></mutation><field name="DEBUG"></field><statement name="ST"><block type="robGlobalVariables_declare" id="阢坷镐印ㄏ疝蚤往冖轭翎箅舰趄蹂溴戾翎忪褰㈡犰箦盹鲠忪褰㈡犰箦⒕柬豸狒轱铄艚Ⅳ蝓澧溴沆狎狒轱钸豉疱舰硫蜥呱磲珏⒕集眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧倔礅镬寮骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰再信⒕硫蜥呱磲珏集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞炯忪镢豉疱舰蝻馓轶趔咩蝈狒暹鏖翳殇舰瀣鼓嘻鲍螺形槿止铆侗轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕柬豸狒轱轸屙蠼⒊扉篝唪疱舰身徵澧炯眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰躺釉咴傩泞旧磲珏集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊陌⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰礅邃身徵暹轫徵澧殇舰涝仝谊摁嵬兴贿迦轾轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰邪阿荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜阿荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁阿炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐阿炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写阿荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰邪雹荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜雹荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁雹炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐雹荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写雹炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰邪并炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜并炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁并荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐并炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写并炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰邪尝荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜尝荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁尝炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐尝荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写尝炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰邪储荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜储荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁储炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐储炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写储荆集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊谋⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰礅邃身徵暹轫徵澧殇舰待镲痰贼犀制镭霓膻轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰邪阿荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜阿荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁阿荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐阿荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写阿荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰邪雹荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜雹炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁雹炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐雹荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写雹荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰邪并荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜并炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁并炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐并炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写并荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰邪尝荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜尝炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁尝炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐尝炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写尝荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰邪储荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜储荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁储荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐储荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写储荆集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰聊牟⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰礅邃身徵暹轫徵澧殇舰鄯胛桂荻吻唐胝！蒋芒轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰邪阿炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜阿炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁阿炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐阿炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写阿炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰邪雹炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜雹炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁雹荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐雹炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写雹炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰邪并炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜并荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁并荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐并荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写并炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰邪尝炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜尝荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁尝荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐尝荆集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写尝炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰邪储炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰斜储炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰胁储炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰谐储炯骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰写储炯骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖尖祜汶豉疱舰蝻馇祜忉熘狎獒忪弩咪邈灬蝈殇舰筱扰使暾唧┉鹰涩湟轭翎箅舰趄蹂溴戾翎忪褰㈡犰箦盹鲠忪褰㈡犰箦⒕柬豸狒轱铄艚Ⅳ蝓澧溴沆狎狒轱钸豉疱舰熙礅弪⒕集眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧菌徨桁弪集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰再信⒕熙礅弪集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞炯忪镢豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰鲑杩哈孙湾蒴戴猃贤鳍轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖尖祜汶豉疱舰蝻馇祜忉熘狎獒忪弩咪邈灬蝈殇舰└疬吴糨ツ挖秭咣丌轭翎箅舰趄蹂溴戾翎忪褰㈡犰箦盹鲠忪褰㈡犰箦⒕柬豸狒轱铄艚Ⅳ蝓澧溴沆狎狒轱钸豉疱舰熙礅弪⒕集眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧倔翎弪脲集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰再信⒕熙礅弪集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞炯忪镢豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰锓禅关裰蜜词龙壶缏桶轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷颈蛋凹骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖尖祜汶豉疱舰蝻馇祜忉熘狎獒忪弩咪邈灬蝈殇舰诹弧腰徐泥螬飓痕鲜琚轭翎箅舰趄蹂溴戾翎忪褰㈡犰箦盹鲠忪褰㈡犰箦⒕柬豸狒轱铄艚㈡犰箦溴沆狎狒轱钸豉疱舰嘛镬遽睥炯眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧眷邃哚罴骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰再信⒕嘛镬遽罴骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞炯忪镢豉疱舰祜玳氵怙镬遽睥殇舰铝≈疲臊瞪瞻喵禳吼发轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰孪咸⒕屏逃偶骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖尖祜汶豉疱舰蝻饷镱趄镬筮祜镳骑蝈鲥颌殇舰忿Ｚ鹰潋讹渍稽旦般脾轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰蝻饬泗轱铙唧弪獒爝痱轭簪殇舰策Ｚ谄┠披胼号掬轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕荐犰蹂钺礤舰险寓炯忪镢豉疱舰蝻庥孱箫蝮唪轫弪哏弭俞眇戾殇舰滥グカ佞到蜻礁桐汨檄轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕柬豸狒轱盹溴舰至陶泞炯眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰拖呐⒕至陶偶骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰优斡弦邢以⒕奔骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰犹显⒕集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖尖祜汶豉疱舰蝻饷镱趄镬筮殒殇舰绺浮谫炜至璞况淹轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕荐犰蹂钺礤舰善阿炯忪镢豉疱舰祜玳氵镳弪狒轱睥殇舰耍赦文耶柏弈卑削佤轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰闲⒕弦集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰立炯忪镢豉疱舰祜玳氵泔眇狎澧殇舰羿牡∵蒉暴┊育倍衷佗轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰闲⒕淘集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰立炯忪镢豉疱舰蝻庥孱箫蝮哚沣屐弪镯弭弪哏弭俞眇戾殇舰ㄆ嚣去嗬癯哓碎档揆茛轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕柬豸狒轱盹溴舰至陶泞炯眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰拖呐⒕至陶偶骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰犹显⒕釉遗吻匀集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰优斡弦邢以⒕吡集骈屐渚艰殇钺礤舰优斡弦邢以鲠祯褰⑦立炯栝溴炯忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄炯忪镢豉疱舰磲翳哚蜷翳礤糸恽殇舰辛滤袄嫠缸粜睐嬗リ赵轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰闲⒕蜕握蛹骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰立炯忪镢豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰澡哺郾偾差分灏┽幔症轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷颈鞍凹骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄炯忪镢豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰鲎捏舳岩骆≯历镲癣轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕柬豸狒轱溽翎豉疱舰熙礅弪⒕集眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧倔翎弪脲集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄炯忪镢豉疱舰祜玳氵泔眇狎澧殇舰书脸嘞打ㄋ裎耪朵邻押轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰闲⒕窃集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰立炯忪镢豉疱舰蝻庥孱箫蝮哚沣屐弪镯弭弪哏弭俞眇戾殇舰鳟眩巍科颗芬オ棺团茛轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕柬豸狒轱盹溴舰至陶泞炯眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰拖呐⒕至陶偶骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰犹显⒕釉遗吻匀集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰优斡弦邢以⒕吡集骈屐渚艰殇钺礤舰优斡弦邢以鲠祯褰⑦立炯栝溴炯忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄炯忪镢豉疱舰磲翳哚蜷翳礤糸恽殇舰麾迕连兵佣是睹徘内轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰闲⒕聊募骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰立炯忪镢豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰蟪装率厣抄卧趸寻呢轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷颈鞍凹骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄炯忪镢豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰椅替箩嗡彻］蜇ヰ彤踽轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕柬豸狒轱溽翎豉疱舰熙礅弪⒕集眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧倔翎弪脲集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南阿炯忪镢豉疱舰翦暨泔眄孱簪殇舰鲲醍襄膛捶顿徐缲撷轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕腻洛筱桁艴铋珲铉篌孱箫栳轫阴桢躞翎钿彘铄洛筱桁艴铋珲铉鲲辩镤弪卑鞍礴集骈屐渚集忪镢刖尖祜汶豉疱舰礅邃渝铙矧筮糸礤蜻蝈箦簪殇舰坠梵玳爆呦拎辰希羊ヴ轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰优斡弦邢以⒕奔骈屐渚集忪镢刖尖祜汶豉疱舰蝻饷镱趄镬筮麽轸唪轫澧殇舰公扯禅骋噗倘瘁滹述盛轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕荐犰蹂钺礤舰琢稍⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰囟承鬲扒亓嵩绯讲并轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷静鞍集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖尖祜汶豉疱舰蝻馔狒柽汨犷珏殇舰偷勒结风愈膀髦切轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕荐犰蹂钺礤舰至尧炯忪镢豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰珏翡殓槿鼹刂鳌鲺刺轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕柬豸狒轱溽翎豉疱舰熙礅弪⒕集眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧菌徨桁弪集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰呐淘立炯忪镢豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰蕤烫嗡锷饪穗冉刃轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷颈集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖尖祜汶豉疱舰蝻饷镱趄镬筮殒殇舰舌董魂羔舌入呓愕沟秀轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕荐犰蹂钺礤舰善阿炯忪镢豉疱舰祜玳氵泔眇狎澧殇舰冕宠蛋泊膝蘼蔺脘毖轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰闲⒕窃集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰立炯忪镢豉疱舰蝻庥孱箫蝮唪轫弪哏弭俞眇戾殇舰芋混禹液矶逻锌畴储轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕柬豸狒轱盹溴舰至陶泞炯眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰拖呐⒕至陶偶骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰优斡弦邢以⒕奔骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰犹显⒕集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄炯忪镢豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰砚嗝爷谯挥篆‘槿末颠轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷痉鞍集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南阿炯忪镢豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦簪殇舰垧嘶蠊殁麻宛雾觋缕轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕柬豸狒轱溽翎豉疱舰熙礅弪⒕集眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧菌徨桁弪集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞炯忪镢豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰阢婷睡谐溴刃解类宓吊轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖尖祜汶豉疱舰蝻饷镱趄镬筮殒殇舰狮狺趔鹩梧蛭歉夜┷并轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕荐犰蹂钺礤舰善阿炯忪镢豉疱舰祜玳氵泔眇狎澧殇舰泶浍セ益槽栝铙赎酥轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰闲⒕叛集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰立炯忪镢豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰蚧承疸獭貊螬痱鹚派＂轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕柬豸狒轱溽翎豉疱舰熙礅弪⒕集眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧菌徨桁弪集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄炯忪镢豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰埘∩奘梨垦符ǚ□立轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷境集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南阿炯忪镢豉疱舰礅邃零糸镱筮溟箴灬唛磲珏殇舰鸲鲦浔┠拾畸尤鞯铊轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕柬豸狒轱豉疱舰赏燎泞炯眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰再信⒕赏燎偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞炯忪镢豉疱舰蝻馓轶趔哏弭深溴殇舰阈０菏偕┅蒙到作毖轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕柬豸狒轱篝狒屙孱艚㈡犰箦狒舰趄蹂溽翎豉疱舰身徵澧炯眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰拖呐⒕桥约骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰兹乓泞酒蚁瓦釉烈约骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞炯忪镢豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰骏顼颢脏稿噗藉够并轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕柬豸狒轱溽翎豉疱舰硫蜥呱磲珏⒕集眭翎糸镱炯骈屐钺礤舰至尧倔礅镬寮骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰猎⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳唑犷滹磉轭簪殇舰姓ú罾阍肱蓊鳢援镢涪轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕荐犰蹂钺礤舰埔贤⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰野娉鬏奢嘏冬胬退瞎轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰韵⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰晋练楂模烙迈踺枣厣轭翎箅舰趄蹂⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷静集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖尖祜汶豉疱舰蝻饷镱趄镬筮殒澎箦殇舰莱须腥尥89O3a" intask="true"><mutation else="1"></mutation><repetitions><value name="IF0"><block type="variables_get" id="d-y!%`Tl_*BCXWR/Dgs5" intask="true"><mutation datatype="Boolean"></mutation><field name="VAR">led_an</field></block></value><statement name="DO0"><block type="variables_set" id="nH=N3X@b)u.*N8kCsxB*" intask="true"><mutation datatype="Boolean"></mutation><field name="VAR">led_an</field><value name="VALUE"><block type="logic_boolean" id="IksTYBq1%R..G-Dg=E36" intask="true"><field name="BOOL">FALSE</field></block></value></block><block type="mbedActions_leds_off" id=",NKYh|[BnC`;qWr=v^3t" intask="true"><field name="ACTORPORT">_R</field><hide name="ACTORPORT" value="_R"></hide></block></statement><statement name="ELSE"><block type="variables_set" id="Mu88!`#I2is:O`Px+b9" intask="true"><mutation datatype="Boolean"></mutation><field name="VAR">led_an</field><value name="VALUE"><block type="logic_boolean" id=")GqD8EE:}AGD8{Mk?jBe" intask="true"><field name="BOOL">TRUE</field></block></value></block><block type="mbedActions_leds_on" id="M(l*|Ec}}FZ-4sN9=_b" intask="true"><field name="ACTORPORT">_R</field><hide name="ACTORPORT" value="_R"></hide><value name="COLOR"><block type="mbedColour_picker" id="Q]uBDZDi0UU]3?bgS6?6" intask="true"><field name="COLOUR">#ff0000</field></block></value></block></statement></repetitions></block><block type="robControls_wait_time" id="LC^Nla6|:Hz0(Gt{n-?s" intask="true"><value name="WAIT"><block type="math_number" id="}QRlCCRtqy?^_p6NCL]H" intask="true"><field name="NUM">200</field></block></value></block><block type="variables_set" id="/!=S3/ggYY@U!fljJvOW" intask="true"><mutation datatype="Number"></mutation><field name="VAR">zaehler</field><value name="VALUE"><block type="math_number" id="{u3DX;bbJyRu:/A!FS:d" intask="true"><field name="NUM">0</field></block></value></block></statement></block></statement></block></instance><instance x="-1192" y="1757"><block type="robControls_wait_time" id="Jmxet!e:zoF_mTeQw|z(" intask="false"><value name="WAIT"><block type="math_number" id="zwsC6WuT+H=I4-PwHHf9" intask="false"><field name="NUM">200</field></block></value></block></instance></block_set></program><config><block_set robottype="calliope" xmlversion="3.1" description="" tags="" xmlns="http://de.fhg.iais.roberta.blockly"><instance x="-34" y="270"><block type="robConf_key" id="Kbp:=x@gw@n.bNH|1|e" intask="true" deletable="false"><field name="NAME">A</field><field name="PIN1">A</field></block></instance><instance x="-34" y="120"><block type="robConf_key" id="wk*JZQvB.fj=I`N#NWp" intask="true" deletable="false"><field name="NAME">B</field><field name="PIN1">B</field></block></instance><instance x="80" y="268"><block type="robConf_accelerometer" id="#(ufvG,s^FcqI,aFn/A{" intask="true" deletable="false"><field name="NAME">_A</field></block></instance><instance x="-34" y="450"><block type="robConf_buzzer" id="}%d2_68IJd*7Oy{qrMR," intask="true" deletable="false"><field name="NAME">_B</field></block></instance><instance x="-34" y="422"><block type="robConf_rgbled" id="lgi%C3,J!smR:eP0aal_" intask="true" deletable="false"><field name="NAME">_R</field></block></instance><instance x="80" y="239"><block type="robConf_compass" id="O%Oi0Tq`hGEvrgHGPYY=" intask="true" deletable="false"><field name="NAME">_C</field></block></instance><instance x="197" y="162"><block type="robConf_sound" id="e:4V0FcDx%9,.7xO,Ns@" intask="true" deletable="false"><field name="NAME">_S</field></block></instance><instance x="80" y="378"><block type="robConf_temperature" id="0y].dnS)P)Jjzeu3/0C" intask="true" deletable="false"><field name="NAME">_T</field></block></instance><instance x="80" y="211"><block type="robConf_gyro" id="lIT?C5y|(7FWCQIUnpc" intask="true" deletable="false"><field name="NAME">_G</field></block></instance><instance x="197" y="190"><block type="robConf_light" id="9Ktt(7_4+XmKC0]5Zha?" intask="true" deletable="false"><field name="NAME">_L</field></block></instance></block_set></config></export>